<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ihor Burlachenko</title>
    <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ihor Burlachenko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ihor.burlachenko.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code sharing between React and React Native applications</title>
      <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/code-sharing-between-react-and-react-native-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/code-sharing-between-react-and-react-native-applications/</guid>
      <description>Sharing code between the web and native was one of the most interesting React Native questions since its appearance. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the original goal of the React Native but when all our code base is written in one language it&amp;rsquo;s a natural desire to remove code duplication and reuse as much code as possible.
The approach I&amp;rsquo;m going to explain is based on the fact that React Native loads platform specific Javascript modules based on their extensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Linking with React Native</title>
      <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/deep-linking-with-react-native/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/deep-linking-with-react-native/</guid>
      <description>Recently I added deep linking integration to one of my projects and I want to share my experience with you. It is a complete guide which covers all the steps and explains how to add deep links both on iOS and Android. In my example, I&amp;rsquo;ll use React Native Router Flux. It is a very nice navigation library and at the moment of writing, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything which I would like more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m Ihor I provide software engineering and consulting services. I have a solid background in developing complex business logic, solving performance issues, and managing teams. With over 12 years of experience, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how to deliver a high-quality product and meet business needs. Drop me a line at services@burlachenko.com for details and availability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/license/</guid>
      <description>Content license All non-code blog content is licensed under Creative Commons BY-NC-SA.
Code license All source code files and snippets found on this blog, unless otherwise explicitly noted, are licensed under the terms below.
Copyright 2019 Ihor Burlachenko Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &amp;quot;License&amp;quot;); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot; BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/react-styled-floating-label-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/react-styled-floating-label-demo/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source</title>
      <link>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ihor.burlachenko.com/open-source/</guid>
      <description>react-styled-floating-label Floating label component which works with any HTML input. Have a look at the demo</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>